so we're driving to David uncle's for
삼촌 에게 데려다 주려고
New Year's dinner and I'm scared about
새해 저녁 식사와 나는 약 무서워
how like the connection might go so I
연결이 어떻게 될지 모르겠다.
joined early just in case I get cut off
내가 막히면 조기에 합류 했다.
early
이른
well I joined early because this is the
나는 일찍 여기에 합류 했다.
first time I've ever been on Google Bank
처음 Google 은행에 처음 입사했습니다.
I had to download it myself
나는 그것을 직접 다운로드 해야했다.
Oh perfect
오 완벽한
and I think we beat everybody else there
우리가 다른 사람들을 때려 눕힌 것 같아.
except I I see Japheth in but I can't
나는 II를 제외하고 Japheth를 본다 . 그러나 나는 할 수 없다.
hear him no I didn't either
내 말 안 들었어.
oh here comes Robbie I think how would
오, 여기 로비 가 오면 어떻게 될까?
your Christmas very nice I I don't know
너의 크리스마스 아주 잘 모르겠다.
Robbie ever said anything I had neck
로비 는 목에 뭐든 말한 적있어.
surgery early December so I had I had I
12 월 초 수술을 받았 으므로
was a tremendous amount of pain from
엄청난 통증이 있었다.
Labor Day to the beginning of December
12 월 초에 근로자의 날
down my arm and I'm feeling wonderful so
내 팔을 내리고 기분이 좋네.
Christmas for me was spectacular
나를위한 크리스마스는 장관이었다.
oh good awesome the year that you've
오, 굉장해 올해는 네가 좋아.
recovered I didn't I didn't have a clue
회복 된 나는 단서가 없었어요.
of surgery but but it's nice to see you
수술의하지만,하지만 당신을보고하는 것이 좋다
you look like you have good range of
당신의 좋은 범위를 가지고처럼 보일
motion and everything so it went really
모션과 모든 것이 정말 갔다.
well then oh it did it did it went
그럼 오, 그게 그랬어?
spectacularly well so I'm good I can
훌륭하게 잘 그래서 나는 좋다.
move around I'm not supposed to move too
주위를 움직여서 나는 움직 이기로되어 있지 않다.
much yet I go back in a couple of weeks
많이 아직 나는 몇 주 후에 돌아 간다.
so you can tell me when I can go back to
그래서 내가 언제 돌아갈 수 있는지 말해 줄 수 있어.
work
작업
well hopefully you get at least until
잘하면 적어도 당신 은 적어도
the spring because it's so really cold
봄이 너무 추웠 기 때문에
right now
지금 당장
this is cold my coworkers are probably
이건 내 동료들이 아마 추워.
calling me every name in the book you
너를 책에있는 모든 이름으로 불렀다.
picked a good time I'm like I choose
나는 좋은 시간을 골랐다. 나는 선택한다.
this how are the roads be brutal yeah
이 길은 잔인한 길입니다. 예.
why should I even take the highway right
왜 고속도로를 타고 가야하지?
now maybe slowly yeah probably the
이제 어쩌면 천천히 그래 아마
highways gonna need to clear it yeah
고속도로는 그것을 지울 필요가있다.
they usually do the highways down here
그들은 보통 여기 고속도로를 이용합니다.
first this Turkey better be worth it
먼저이 터키는 가치가있다.
definitely will be I J I got an insta
분명히 IJI는 insta가있을거야.
pot one of those electric pressure
그 전기 압력 중 하나
cookers nice for myself for Christmas so
크리스마스 자신을 위해 좋은 요리기구 이렇게
I've been cooking up a storm at home so
나는 집에서 폭풍우 를 요리하고 있어.
now I have tons of leftovers in the
지금 나는 남은 톤을 가지고있다.
fridge so we're gonna go gonna go eat
냉장고 그래서 우리는 먹을 거야.
more soon and you're gonna take home
더 빨리 집에 갈거야.
leftovers right of course there's a way
남은 권리 물론 방법이
I can put this on somewhere my arm I
어디 선가 나의 팔 I에 넣을 수 있습니다
know the trick I don't want it down here
트릭을 알고 난 여기를 원하지 않는다
you can feel a double chin action it's
당신은 그것의 이중 턱 액션을 느낄 수있다
not 1 o'clock yeah we're real or else we
1 시가 아니야 우리는 진짜야 그렇지 않으면 우리
are very early yes you see other people
아주 일찍 예, 당신은 다른 사람들을 봅니다.
flashing on the bottom of my screen here
내 화면 하단에 깜박임
but I don't see names
하지만 나는 이름이 보이지 않는다.
okay gotta get up and move around a
알았어 일어나 일어나서
little bit mmm
약간의 mmm
here we go drive these somebody on
여기 우리 가이 사람을 운전하게 하네.
though something bad happened really but
뭔가 나쁜 일이 실제로 있었지만
at least now you're witness to the fact
적어도 지금 너는 사실을 목격하고있다.
that I was part of the hangouts because
내가 행 아웃에 참여했기 때문에
I do know that where we're going which
나는 우리가 어디로 가고 있는지를 알고있다 .
is like a 40-minute drive I never have
나는 결코 없다 차로 40 분 거리에 같다
service by the time we get there so are
우리가 거기에 도착되는 시간에 의해 서비스
you driving yours we're driving south
우리가 남쪽으로 운전하고있어.
southwest stuff down in the northbound
북향에서 남서쪽 물건 아래로
Highway yeah yeah cuz cuz Robbie always
고속도로 네 그래 사촌 사촌 로비 항상
says he goes away he goes north and I
그는 그가 북쪽으로 간다.
just like north of where you are come on
네가 온 북쪽처럼
my goodness
이럴 수가
[Laughter]
[웃음]
there is a little bit of that to New
거기 에 새로운 조금있다.
York yeah I live I live 80 miles north
요크 나는 80 마일 북쪽에 살고있다.
of New York City and that's north enough
뉴욕시의
for me thank you okay so is that close
내가 좋아 감사에 대한 그래서 가까운
to the border then oh no no no I don't
국경에 오, 안돼, 안돼, 안돼, 안돼.
know I don't know geography at all we're
내가 지리를 모르는 걸 알아.
about to New York are you yeah Betty
뉴욕에 대해서 당신 은 베티예요?
miles world of the city which of New
새로운 도시의 마일 세계
York City which is the southernmost tip
최남단 팁 인 요크 시티
of New York you can't get further south
뉴욕 남쪽으로 갈 수는 없다.
in New York State
뉴욕 주
okay cool what's it called New Paltz
좋아, New Paltz 라는게 뭐야?
it's a little college town okay very is
그것은 아주 작은 대학 도시 입니다.
that it's big now it's a city now yeah
그것은 지금 큰 도시입니다.
yeah
네
nice holy look at the highway hold on oh
고속도로 에서 좋은 신성한 모습이 오 개최
my god oh look at this it's crawling
내 신 아 이걸 봐. 크롤 링 이야.
okay so we'll be on the call for a long
좋아요. 그래서 우리는 오랫동안 전화를받을 것입니다.
time I dig this David Rohde maybe we'll
내가 데이빗 로데를 파헤 치면 아마 우리가 할거야.
take the next exit then going down maybe
어쩌면 그 다음 출구 로 가라.
a it might not be too bad
그것은 나쁘지 않을지도 모른다.
let's I'm doing 40 shut up Greg in a
내가 그렉 을 40 명이라도 입 다물고있어 .
hundred zone what a day it is second
백분 의 일 구역 그것은 두 번째 무엇입니까?
gear on 100 kilometer high way wow this
100 킬로미터의 높은 길 에서 기어가
is really crazy and we are
정말 미쳤어.
[Music]
[음악]
well that's what you should have slaw
그게 당신이 slaw 를 가져야 만하는 것입니다.
yeah well yeah everything everybody's
그래, 네 , 모든게 다 예요.
driving slow widgets for the bastards
나쁜 놈들을 위해 천천히 위젯을 몰고 간다.
pretty white out oh yeah Oh Robbie
오, 그래, 오, 그래, 예쁜 흰색 오, 로비
sunshine face oh yeah so he's not live
햇빛 얼굴 오, 예, 그래서 그는 살지 않습니다.
yet either
아직
nobody else is live but I oh my god
아무도 살지는 않지만 오, 세상에.
totally different Street hunters wish I
완전히 다른 스트리트 사냥꾼들은 내가 바란다.
had of something to drink like a hot
뜨거운 것처럼 마실 것
chocolate aliens put your around oh my
초콜릿 외계인이 내 주위에 넣어 오, 내
goodness
선량
[Music]
[음악]
7:15 K and a hundred zone we'll get a
7시 15 분 케이와 100 영역 우리가 얻을거야
speeding ticket could explain why we saw
과속 티켓 은 왜 우리가 보았는지 설명 할 수 있습니다.
the helicopter how longs it take to cook
헬리콥터가 요리하는 데 얼마나 오래 걸리는지
turkey kill now solo it yeah hey is
칠면조 지금 솔로 그것을 죽일 수있다.
Robbie I see him Oh see there we go come
로비 나는 그를 만난다. 오 거기에 우리가 간다.
on Robbie doing doing like it now track
로비가 같은 일을하고있는 지금 추적
maybe
아마도
ten minutes we have cool in-car audio
차가운 오디오를 10 분내에 얻을 수 있습니다.
I'm in recliner
나는 안락 의자에있다.
yes exactly Oh put it in in context
예 정확히 아 맥락에서 그것을 넣어
usually to get to this point it takes
보통이 시점으로 가려면
about three minutes from from getting on
점점 에서 약 3 분
the highway yeah you'll be fine yeah
고속도로 네, 괜찮을거야. 예.
Lowen turpis just this section or is
이 부분 만 turpis 낮추 거나
this gonna keep on going right into this
이 일이 바로 계속 될거야.
Florida State market it's actually best
플로리다 주 시장은 실제로 최고입니다.
to call I'm even giving me a headache
심지어 나에게 두통을주고있다 호출
I hate not speeding usually has a
나는 과속하지 않는 것이 싫다.
motorcycle well not in this weather
이 날씨 에 오토바이 잘 안다.
yeah worry buddy we tend to take the
예, 친구를 걱정하는 경향이 있습니다.
highway because you get less interaction
고속도로는 상호 작용이 적기 때문에
with intersections and people pulling
교차로와 사람들이 당기는
out of places unexpectedly at least on
예기치 않게 적어도 예기치 않게
the high or you just straight yeah you
높은 또는 당신 은 바로 당신 을 똑바로 예
have a lot of holes they're really the
그들이 정말로 많은 구멍을 가지고있다.
only part of New York I've ever been to
뉴욕에 가본 적이없는
with a lot of tools New York takes your
많은 도구로 뉴욕 이 당신을 데려갑니다.
money any way they can we have the the
돈을 어떻게 든 우리가 가질 수있는
EZ Pass tags so that you can drive right
EZ 패스 태그를 사용하면 오른쪽으로 운전할 수 있습니다.
through the tolls you know instead of
대신 알고있는 통행료를 통해
stopping money over and with the couple
부부와 함께 돈을 멈추다.
of visits to the hospital because I go
내가 가기 때문에 병원 방문의
to that I had the surgery in New York
뉴욕에 수술을 받았기 때문에
City they refill my easy past four times
그들이 네 번 쉬운 과거를 네 번 보충하는 도시
because of the tolls are so
통행료가 너무하다의 때문에
it's crazy
미쳤어.
now are there non tool options there are
지금 거기에 비 도구 옵션이 있습니다
and it will take you about ten times
그리고 그것은 당신에게 약 10 번 걸릴 것입니다.
longer to get there god yeah oh yeah
오, 네, 네, 오 예
it's they're all you know state roads
그것들은 모두 당신이 알고있는 주 도로입니다.
with you got to drive through little
너는 조금씩 운전 해야 해.
towns and slow down you know we take the
우리 마을을
interstates if you ever been in New York
뉴욕에 온 적이 있다면 인터 스테이트
you know you have the Thruway out there
너는 저기서 쓰루 웨이가 있음 을 너도 알지.
that ends up in Buffalo that comes all
그는 모든 온다 버팔로에 끝
but New York City is just it's crazy
그러나 뉴욕시는 미친 것입니다.
it cost fifteen bucks just to get into
그것은 단지에 들어갈 십오 달러의 비용
New York City over oh my god yeah Wow
뉴욕시 이상 오 나의 맙소사 와우
I had a guy when I did training up in
난에서 훈련 않은 사람이 있었다
Rochester New York a few years ago a guy
로체스터 뉴욕 몇 년 전 한 남자
drove from Florida he says I can't
플로리다에서 운전 그는 말한다 그럴 수 없어
believe I can drive from Florida all the
플로리다에서 온 것 같아.
way up to Washington DC with no tools
방법 워싱턴 DC까지없는 도구
and then once I get Washington DC I get
워싱턴 DC에 도착하면
into up to New York I pay like 50 or $60
뉴욕 까지 50 달러 또는 60 달러를 지불합니다.
in tolls Robbie keeps getting up and
통행료는 Robbie가 계속 올라갑니다.
walking away can he hear us I wonder the
멀리 걷기 것은 그가 우리를들을 수 있습니다 내가 궁금해
judging from your reaction I guess you
당신의 반응으로 판단 해 봤는데
guys don't have a lot of goals we have
우리는 많은 목표를 가지고 있지 않다.
one whole route and I don't think I've
하나의 전체 경로 와 나는 생각 하지 않는다.
used it even more than three times in my
내 3 번 이상 사용 했어.
whole life because are you hear nothing
평생 동안 너는 들리지 않는다.
but nightmares because you have to have
하지만 악몽은, 당신은해야하기 때문에
a transponder
트랜스 폰더
it'll bill your your I guess based on
그것은 당신의 청구서를 근거로 생각합니다.
your license plate it takes a picture of
당신의 번호판이의 사진을 촬영
your license plate so you don't drive
라이센스 판은 그래서 당신은 운전을하지 않습니다
through a goose at all but because of
거위를 통해 모든 만의 때문에
that there's been problems with people
사람들에게 문제 가 있다는
being double bills or you know I'm miss
두 배의 지폐가되거나 내가 알기 론
reading the camera
카메라 읽기
it seems a little bit too primitive yet
아직 너무 원시적 인 것처럼 보입니다.
with that they're starting that now here
그걸로 지금 여기에서 시작하고 있어.
and it's like keep moving you know if
그리고 그것은 계속 당신이 알고있는 것처럼 움직입니다.
you don't have the if you have the EZ
네가 EZ를 가졌다 면 네가 가질 수 없어.
Pass it will deduct it from your account
패스하면 계정에서 공제 됩니다.
if you don't and they will mail you a
당신이하지 않으면 그들은 당신에게 메일을 보낼 것입니다.
bill I was like really
청구서 나는 정말로 같았다.
snail mail you're gonna mail me a bill
달팽이 메일로 청구서를 보내 주겠어.
for a bridge yeah and there were people
네 다리 에 사람들이 있었어.
to take that bridge you know they go to
그 다리 걸릴 당신은 그들이 갈 알아
work they take it five times a week how
그들은 그것을 다섯 번 일주일 방법을 작동
often do you bill get the tag it's
자주 청구서에 태그를 붙이십니까?
easier yeah I'm happy Anatole haven't
더 쉬운 예, Anatole 은 행복 하지 않습니다.
been too much a thing here I just took
너무 많은 일이있어. 내가 방금 가져 갔어.
the train for the first time to Toronto
토론토에 처음 으로 기차
and they have a thing called a presto
그리고 그들은 프레스토라는 환상을 가지고
pass or you can use a card and fill it
통과하거나 카드를 사용하여 채울 수 있습니다.
up sort of I guess like the same ideas
종류까지 나도 같은 생각과 같은 생각의
or anything hot and and if you take the
또는 뜨거운 것 그리고 당신이 가지고가는 경우에.
train a certain number of times you get
네가 얻을 수 있는 횟수를 훈련시키다 .
a discount on your actual trip itself
실제 여행 자체 할인
right right I did I've taken it one we
맞아 내가 그걸 가져 갔어.
had those cards for the new york city
뉴욕시를 위해 그 카드를 가지고 있었다.
buses and subways a little max trip card
버스와 지하철 에서 약간의 최대 여행 카드
like a credit card you zip it right
신용 카드처럼 너는 그걸 제대로 압축 해.
through yeah
을 통해 그래
yeah very handy so soon there'll be no
그래, 곧 아주 편리 할거야.
cash for anything anymore no it'll be
더 이상 현금이 없어.
all all cards yep
모든 모든 카드가 옙
Bitcoin Bitcoin which we don't own any
우리가 소유하지 않은 Bitcoin Bitcoin
of your too many horror stories about
너무 많은 공포 이야기 에 대해
that stuff it doesn't make it I tried to
그 물건 은 내가 그것을 하려고 하지 않는다.
watch the documentary on it and it
그것은 그것의 다큐멘터리를보고
didn't make sense to me even when they
경우에도 나에게 이해가되지 않았다 그들이
were explaining it slowly in the
천천히 설명했다.
documentary so yeah I feel like we'll
다큐멘터리 그래 그래, 우리가 좋아할 것 같아.
never be I'll never be a Bitcoin owner
절대로 Bitcoin 소유자가 될 수 없다 .
yeah and it seems to be treated like a
예 , 그리고 그것은 마치 치료받은 것처럼 보입니다.
commodity on the exchanges as I wait a
내가 기다리는대로 상품 교환
minute.what
분. 뭔지.
thanks yeah I don't I don't get it
고마워 그래, 난 못해.
with all of these I'll let my daughter
이들 모두와 함께 내 딸을 드리겠습니다
I'm too old I'm gonna die with money
나는 너무 늙어서 돈으로 죽을거야.
forget forget the computer so I spoke to
내가 말했던 것을 잊지 마라.
you soon the highway sped up and then it
곧 고속도로가 가속화되고
slowed right back down into the Herbie
허비 로 다시 오른쪽으로 늦췄다.
you look like you're moving okay we're
당신은 당신이 좋아 이동하는 것처럼 우리가있어 보이는
doing 31 kilometers
31 킬로미터하고있다.
yeah usually this highway runs at about
네, 보통 이 고속도로는
110 kilometers an hour yeah moving is
110 킬로미터 움직이는 한 시간 예요.
good see in New York City usually stop
뉴욕시에서 볼 때 대개 그만
and then move ten feet then stop that's
10 피트를 움직여서 그만하면됩니다.
that's frustrating constant moving even
좌절감없이 끊임없이 움직입니다.
if it's slow is still constant moving
천천히 움직이는 경우 계속 움직입니다.
yeah
네
and it's a standard so it makes it
그리고 그것을 표준으로 만들었습니다.
easier if there's constant movement yep
일정한 움직임이 있으면 더 쉽게 옙
Oh Robbie just went got his coffee so he
오 로비는 방금 커피를 마 셨으니 까.
said still not talking to us though I
여전히 우리에게 I 불구하고 이야기하지 않고, 상기
think he's grabbing his headset yeah
그는 그래 그의 헤드셋을 잡는 것 같아요
here we go
여기에 우리가 간다.
101 everybody else is late now
101 누구나 늦었 어.
such a process because hey guys hey
이봐, 얘들 아.
we've been talking about you can you
우리는 할 수있는 당신에 대해 얘기했습니다
hear me now as you can see Sasha and
당신이 사샤와
Dave are on the road yeah it looks like
데이브 가 길 위에있다.
right safe oh my goodness
옳은 안전 오 세상에
welcome to Canada just getting to the
캐나다에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
studio a little bit it's not too bad of
스튜디오는 너무 나쁘지 않다.
a drive but even so my wife was like are
드라이브하지만 심지어 내 아내는 같았다
you sure you want to do this for bill
청구서 를 위해 이걸 하고 싶으 시겠습니까?
absolutely thank you hey Bill how you
절대적으로 당신에게 헤이 빌 어떻게 감사
doing I'm doing well you I am doing I
내가하고있는 일을 잘하고있어.
think your your clocks are a little
너의 시계가 조금 있다고 생각해.
faster than mine mine says two minutes -
내 것보다 빠르다 내 것이 2 분이라고 -
so are we late I got two minutes - one
그래서 우리는 늦은 지 2 분이 남았습니다.
okay so it'sit's sashes clock oh there
오케이 거기에 시계가 있네.
you go oh I would I'm punctual come on I
당신은 내가 I에 엄수 올거야 것 오 이동
wasn't sure if I'd be able to actually
내가 실제로 할 수 있을지 확신 하지 못했습니다.
log on ice hey Dave hey how's it going
얼음에 로그온 헤이 데이브 헤이 어떻게 지내?
good you keeping her safe on the road
도로에서 그녀를 안전하게 지키면 좋겠다.
they're paying attention yeah yeah
그들은 예를 주목 하고있어 그래, 그래
terrible yeah how far out of town of you
끔찍한 예 얼마나 멀리 마을에서
guys we're not even out of town yet oh
우리는 아직 마을 밖에서조차도 아니야. 오.
really
정말
on your way out yeah we're just passing
네가가는 길에 우리는 그냥 지나가고있다.
SRAM right now 15 minutes to make it
지금 SRAM 을 만드는 데 15 분이 걸립니다.
from Bayfield on-ramp they're not even
Bayfield on-ramp에서 그들은 심지어 평평하지 않습니다.
Boston
보스턴
we're heading to Lefroy okay and not
우리는 레프로에게 괜찮을 거야 , 안돼.
that far but I will lose connection at
멀리까지 나는 연결 을 잃을 것이다 .
some point because before I doesn't have
어떤 점 은 내가 가지기 전에
any oh yes how cool is it though okay so
어떤 아, 네 괜찮아요 그래서 비록 어떻게 멋지다
we can start now it's it's time for our
우리는 이제 시작할 수 있습니다.
google hangout but how cool is it that
구글 행 아웃하지만 얼마나 멋진입니다
you can be on the road and doing this oh
너는 길 에있을 수 있고 이런 일을 할 수있다.
here let me turn around turn this around
여기 주위를 돌리 겠습니다.
oh well yeah here let me switch that
오, 그래, 네, 스위치를 바꾸자.
actually looks bad
실제로 나빠 보인다.
no it's moving yep yeah I'm still
아니, 움직이고 있어. 그래, 난 아직도 그래.
learning how Google Hangouts works so as
구글 행 아웃에서 않도록 작동 방법을 학습
soon as I manually switch a camera I
곧 카메라를 수동으로 전환 할 때
lose all control let's see if that works
모든 컨트롤을 잃어 버리면 작동하는지 봅시다.
there I like that
나는 그것을 좋아 한다.
how cool is it that we can do something
우리가 뭔가 를 할 수있는 것이 얼마나 멋진가
like this in a like a small studio like
같은 작은 스튜디오 에서처럼
we have if technology and you're on the
우리는 기술이 있다면 당신은
road and here we can have a hangout with
도로와 여기에서 함께 수다방을 가질 수 있습니다 .
some of our viewers and it it blows my
시청자의 일부 그것은 내 불면
mind to like I was watching the the
마음 에 나는
countdown last night and they had people
지난 밤 카운트 다운에 사람들이 있었어.
cutting in from various points in Canada
캐나다의 다양한 지점에서 절단
and their technology seemed like there
그들의 기술은이 같은 듯
was like a 20 second delay and you know
20 초 지연과 같았 습니다.
it wasn't that great meanwhile you're
당신이있어 한편이 크지 않았다
driving in real time I love it but we
실시간으로 운전 하면서 나는 그것을 좋아하지만 우리는
just finished watching this this
방금 이것을 보았습니다.
season's black mirrors so I love
내가 좋아하는 계절의 검은 거울들.
technology but at the same time and now
기술이지만 동시에 그리고 지금은
I'm very afraid I'm not sure how far
내가 얼마나 멀리 있는지 모르겠다.
into black near we are it was like I
근처에 검은 색으로 우리는 나처럼
don't know I think we're like season
우리가 시즌 같다고 생각하는지 모르겠다.
what are they in now season four yeah so
그들은 지금 시즌 네 그래 그렇게에서 무엇인가
we're probably like middle of season
우리는 아마도 시즌 중반 인 것 같습니다.
three okay lounge it it's really
세 괜찮아 라운지 그것 정말이야.
important to know you do not have to
당신이 중요하지 않다는 것을 아는 것이 중요 합니다.
watch them in order and I'd really love
순서대로 그들을보고 나는 정말로 좋아할거야.
it if everybody could just watch episode
모두가 단지 에피소드를 볼 수 있다면
1 of season 4 before the next show
다음 쇼 전에 시즌 4의 1
ok before the next yeah spectacular
멋진 예전에 예전에 괜찮 았어.
it's called USS Callister did the
USS Callister 가 전화 했어 .
episode mean we'll have to check it out
에피소드는 우리가 그것을 확인해야합니다 의미
it always leaves me thinking okay and
항상 나를 좋아 생각 떠나
that's why I can't be in a show like
그래서 내가 쇼에 출연 할 수 없어.
black mirror because it leaves you at
검은 거울은 당신을 떠나기 때문에
the end of it you're like okay now I
그것 의 끝 당신은 지금 좋아 좋아.
need to ponder this for three days
이것을 3 일간 숙고 해야 한다.
almost first encounter was last year I
거의 첫 만남은 작년 I이었다
had not completely shared it with him
그와 완전히 공유 하지 않았다.
and now we're watching that's cool well
이제 우리는 잘 보입니다.
hey everybody
헤이 여러분
so I wasn't sure what what kind of
그래서 나는 어떤 종류의
turnout we'd have today because this is
오늘 우리가 가진 투표율 은
our first patron exclusive hangout and
우리 첫 번째 후원자 독점 수다방
category fives first hangout in as many
카테고리가 처음으로 행 아웃에 참여 함
years I think the last one we did was
몇 년 동안 나는 우리 가 한 마지막 일 이
February of 2015 we believe it's been
2015 년 2 월 우리는 그것이
that long but so bill it's nice to have
그 긴하지만 너무 청구가있는 것이 좋다
you here looks like you're our first and
너는 우리가 처음이자
only patron to join today so I hope you
후원자 만 오늘 가입하십시오.
came prepared with loads of questions
많은 질문을 준비 했다.
and comments and everything else this
댓글 및 기타 모든 항목
will be posted for public viewing after
이후 공개적으로 볼 수 있도록 게시됩니다.
but of course you have to be a
물론 당신 은
qualifying patron in order to
순서에 후원자 자격
participate in the actual interaction
실제 상호 작용에 참여하다
with us so so hey Bill
빌 우리와 너무 너무 봐
i I see Jeff is connected but doesn't
나는 Jeff 가 연결되어 있지만 보이지 않는다고 봅니다.
have a camera or microphone so that's
카메라 나 마이크를 가지고 있으니
kind of counterintuitive obviously on
가지 반 직관적 분명히에
the road and she's who yamaguchi is here
길과 그녀는 야마구치가 여기에있다.
with us hey Cesar she's of course you
우리와 헤이 Cesar 그녀는 물론 당신이야.
probably remember her she was on the
아마도 그녀 를 기억하고 있을거야 .
show fairly recently just back in the
상당히 최근에
summer I'm talking about organization
여름 나는 조직에 대해 말하고있다.
and you know you know more about it my
그리고 당신은 그것에 대해 더 많이 알고 있다는 것을 압니다.
wife knows more about it because she got
아내가 알기 때문에 아내는 그것에 대해 더 많이 알고 있습니다.
a hold of the book and my sock drawer is
책과 내 양말 서랍을 잡고있다.
completely
완전히
now but she's who now has taken on the
하지만 지금 그녀는 지금 촬영하고있다 누가
role bill you know on the newsroom setup
뉴스 룸 설정 에서 알고있는 역할 청구서
we have the kind of the side graphics
사이드 그래픽의 종류 가 있습니다 .
and everything like that right so while
그리고 그 모든 것이 그렇게 좋아요.
sash is speaking about a particular
새시 가 특정 것에 대해 말하고있다.
story there's a nice graphic up there I
거기에 멋진 그래픽이 있다.
used to have to come in and you know I'd
사용하기에 올 필요하고 당신은 내가 좋겠 알고
find the images on Google Images or
Google 이미지 또는
wherever the source from the story and
어디든지 이야기에서 소스와
try to put something together but it was
함께 뭔가를 넣어하려고 만했다
just one more thing for me to do and
단지 내가 어떻게 할 한 가지 더와
then she's who took that on so that's
그 다음에 그녀가 그렇게했다.
one thing off of my plate and she's been
내 접시 에서 한 가지 벗어난 그녀는
doing a fantastic job she's doing a way
그녀는 환상적인 일을하고있다.
better job than I could ever do and so
내가 어떻게 그렇게 할 수있는 것보다 더 나은 일
that's been a real bonus for the show so
쇼를위한 정말 보너스 였어.
nice easy I can barely hear you
간신히 듣기가 쉽다.
you guys Here I am from New Paltz New
너희들 여기 뉴 팔츠에서 왔어.
York about 80 miles north of New York
뉴욕 북쪽 약 80 마일
City and as I was saying to Sascha
도시와 나는 Sascha 에게 말하고 있었다.
earlier
일찍이
that's far enough in order for me thank
내가 감사를 위해 그 순서대로 충분히 멀리
you very much
너 대단히
month and a half now I downloaded all
한 달 반 동안 나는 모두를 다운로드했다.
the episodes I recently had surgery at
에피소드는 최근 수술을 받았습니다.
the beginning of December so I had a lot
12 월 초에 많이 먹었 어요.
of time on my hands so I started
내 손 에 시간이 있어서 시작 했어.
watching from episode one it's come a
에피소드 1 에서 시청 한 동영상 입니다.
long way I'm in season I believe eight
나는 절대로 8 시라고 믿는다.
now
지금
oh good time I'm there I've been jumping
오, 즐거운 시간 나는 거기에있다 나는 뛰어 내리고있다.
around the new ones cuz you know because
새로운 것들 주위에 당신이 알고 있기 때문에
they saw the whole dare I say it by
그들은 전체 나는하여 말을 감히 보았다
killer thing say again is that how you
살인자 가 다시 말하면
started watching with just my killer
내 살인마와 함께보기 시작했다.
[Music]
[음악]
definitely one of the first but I'm
확실히 첫 번째 중 하나 지만 나는
actually going into my basement now so I
실제로 내 지하실에 들어가서
can show you my pine killer see if I can
내 소나무 살인자가 내가 볼 수 있는지 보여줄 수있어.
do this now now I wish that we were in
이 지금해라. 나는 우리가
an arthouse I'd show everybody the
내가 모두에게 보여줄 arthouse
computer in glory yeah I got it I gotta
영광의 컴퓨터 그래 내가 꼭있어
watch the episodes with the bill
청구서 와 함께 에피소드보기
alright I got lights on
괜찮아. 불이 켜져있어.
I'm gonna see this Bell I'm just gonna
나는 이걸 보러 갈거야. 난 그냥
I'm gonna turn up my speakers because
내 연설자를 불러올거야 왜냐하면
I'm having trouble hearing you guys I'll
나는 너희들의 말을 듣는 데 어려움을 겪고있다.
be right back okay this is my this is my
이것이 바로 돌아 괜찮을 내이 내
shelf unit down in my basement and so
선반 단위가 내 지하실 에서
here's the if I can get right up there's
내가 바로 갈 수 있다면 여기 있다.
there's the PI killer they owed ROI
그들이 ROI를 빚지고 있는 PI 살인자가 있습니다.
system and that guy is replacing this
시스템이 그 사람을 대신하고있어.
guy that that monster
그 괴물 이라는 남자
so I've already called the oh my Oh
그래서 나는 이미 오 오하이오 라고 불렀다.
droid name - David so it's gonna kill
드로이드 이름 - 데이빗 그래서 죽일거야.
this Goliath of a machine right now
지금이 기계의 골리앗
because I also did get the that little
나는 또한 그 작은 것을 얻었 기 때문에
unit where you plug into your
유닛 에 연결하는
electricity usage and this beast uses
전기 사용 및이 짐승 사용
about $50 of electricity a month Wow
한달 에 약 $ 50 의 전기 와우
yeah so this this is going to be the Leo
그래,이게 바로 레오 가 될거야.
droid unit I've become mine ass and it's
droid unit 나는 내 엉덩이 가 되었어.
gonna pay for itself in about five
약 5 시간 만에 돈을 내겠다.
months
개월
incredible yeah yeah I mean I don't I
놀라운 그래 난 내가하지 의미
don't really want to totally
완전히 원하지 않는다.
decommission that giant because I mean
그 거인을 퇴역 시키라는 뜻이야.
it's got two Xeon processors it's got 32
32 개의 프로세서 가있는 2 개의 제온 프로세서가 있습니다.
gigs of ram it's got a 500 gig hard
램의 공연은 하드 500 기가있어
drive with the OS on it for one terabyte
1 테라 바이트 당 OS를 탑재 한 드라이브
drives in raid fives I'm reluctant to
내가 몰랐던 raid fives의 드라이브
just dump it so but having it on 24/7 is
그냥 덤프하지만 24/7에 있어야합니다 .
just painful yeah so bill yeah you
그냥 고통스러운 예 그래서 빌 법원
you're what we're looking at is
너 우리가 바라는거야.
something that you've seen on the show
쇼에서 본 무언가
plus you picked up the tester to be able
테스터 를 데려 와서
to to find out how much power it was
그것이 얼마나 힘 이 있었 는지 알아 내기 위해
already found have you found the show as
이미 발견 된 공연을
far as showing you I guess relevant
지금까지 당신을 보여주는 나는 관련 추측
technology obviously this is influenced
기술은 분명히 영향을받습니다.
your purchasing decisions so yeah really
당신의 구매 결정은 정말 그렇습니다.
nice because you know it's funny I I
너는 재미 있다고 알고 있기 때문에 좋다. II
handle the financials in the house and I
집안 의 금융을 다루다.
noticed the spike in the electric bill
전기 요금에 스파이크가 나타났습니다 .
oh yeah I couldn't figure it out and I
오 그래 나는 그것을 이해할 수 없었다. 그리고 나
saw that and I said alright let's let's
그것을 보았고 나는 괜찮다고 합시다.
do this so I shut the I shut this guy
이렇게 해 내가이 녀석을 닫았 어.
down
내려가는
shut this this down this Dell and
이것을 이 Dell과
plugged in that unit and left it running
그 장치에 꽂혀 있고 그것을 달리기로 남겼습니다.
and did the calculations and I said ah
계산을했고 나는 아를 말했다.
that's where it is it's that guy isn't
그게 그 녀석이 아닌 곳이야.
that unreal to think that your
라고 생각하는 그 비현실적 당신의
refrigerator is taking less energy but
냉장고가 에너지를 덜 사용하고 있지만
possibly than that little computer for
가능성에 대한 그 작은 컴퓨터가 아닌
now it doesn't help because you see
당신이보기 때문에 지금 도움 이되지 않습니다.
there's there's the oh joy is sitting on
거기에 오, 기쁨 이 앉아있다.
top of another PC and then there's an up
다른 PC의 상단 그리고 나서
PC excellent and yet another server
우수한 PC와 아직 또 다른 서버
excellent this is this is just the
우수한이이 단지를입니다
basement this is Wow this doesn't
지하실이 와우이되지 않습니다됩니다
include my Mac Mini and my my Red Hat
내 Mac Mini와 내 Red Hat 포함
box upstairs and then there's oh yeah I
상자 위층 에 다음 오, 그래 내가있어
work laptop and my home laptop and my
직장 노트북 및 내 집 랩톱 및 내
wife's works laptop at home laptop and
아내의 작품 노트북 가정에서 랩톱 및
now that my daughter's home from college
이제는 내 딸이 대학에서 온 집이야.
her Mac all the little gadgets like I'm
그녀의 맥처럼 모든 작은 도구들 .
holding my iPad or five iPods and
내 iPad 또는 5 개의 iPod 및
Android phones
Android 휴대 전화
mm-hmm so what do you use in the servers
mm-hmm 그래서 서버에서 무엇 을 사용합니까?
and the Odroid for the Odroid is gonna
그리고 Odroid를위한 Odroid는 갈거야.
be my ass it's gonna be my file server I
내 엉덩이를 수 그것의 거 내 파일 서버 I 수
got I got 2 4 terabyte and drives in
내가 2 테라 바이트의 드라이브를 가지고있어 .
hand nice and I'm upper grade one here
손이 멋지다. 나는 여기 1 학년이다 .
one thing I did notice it's funny though
내가 한가지는 재미 있다고 생각합니다.
the see if I can get this for me yeah I
내가 나를 위해 이것을 얻을 수 있는지 보자.
probably can't see it when I opened it
내가 열 때 아마 그것을 볼 수 없다.
up I looked at the pieces and tried to
위로 나는 그 조각들을보고 시도했다.
match it up to the pieces that Edward
에드워드 와 그 조각을 일치 시켜라.
there are two different cloud shell -
거기에 두 가지 구름 껍질 -
Kate I don't know if it's ones for the Q
케이트 나는 그것이 Q를 위한 것인지 몰라.
and ones for the 9 X 4 X u4q there's the
그리고 9 X 4 X의 u4q에 대한 사람이 년대
xu4 and the X you feel Q yeah I'm not
xu4와 X 당신은 그래 아니에요 Q 느낌
sure if they're different cuz if you go
당신 이 간다면 그들이 사촌들 과 다를 지 확신 해.
on the hard colonel website they both
하드 대령 웹 사이트에 둘 다
lists as for the X you for slightly
X에 대한 약간의 목록
different I wonder I wonder if they've
다른 나는 그들이 궁금한지 궁금해.
actually just kind of changed because I
실제로 나는 단지 종류 가 바뀌 었습니다.
saw your post on on YouTube I believe it
YouTube에서 내 소식을 보았습니다.
was mentioning that the design was a
그 디자인이
little bit different so I wonder like
조금 다른 그래서 내가 궁금해.
any company they've they've improved it
그들이 개선 한 회사
a little bit or change something about
조금이라도 바뀌거나 뭔가 바뀌었다.
it
그것
is the only difference with the Q versus
Q와 유일한 차이점은
the non Q model of the XE for was just
for XE 의 비 Q 모델은
the fan the fan wrestles they think
그들이 생각 하는 팬 팬
right right either one well we can now
우리가 지금 할 수있는 우물 중 하나.
yeah now I mean I got fight it's not
그래, 지금은 내가 싸움을 가지고 아니에요 의미
very difficult to figure out because
알아 내기 가 힘들다. 왜냐하면
you're only talking about two different
너는 두 가지 다른 것에 대해서만 이야기 하고있다.
pieces like you have the two little
너 처럼 두 조각 이 조금있다.
hanger pieces that ya know used to
나중에 익숙해 진 걸이 조각들.
attach to the port there is no hanging
항구에 붙어 있지 않고 매달려 있지 않다.
there are no hanger pieces it actually
행거 조각이 실제로 없다.
hangs from the top cover now
지금 윗면 덮개 에서 달려 있다.
oh and you had a like those of those hex
아, 그리고 당신은 그 진수의 그 같은했다
shaped standoffs or about an inch long
모양의 스탠드 오프 또는 약 1 인치 길이
these are only about 3/8 of new song
이들은 새 노래의 약 3/8에 불과합니다.
okay now that the only thing is as I'm
좋아 , 내가 유일하게하는 건 지금 이야.
looking between the because I am using
내가 사용하고 있기 때문에 사이를 바라 보았다.
spinning hard drive there's only about a
약 만 거기에 하드 드라이브 회전
quarter of an inch of space between the
공간 사이의 1/4 인치
upper spinning hard drive and the the
상단 회전 하드 드라이브 와
top of the passive heatsink so it's
패시브 히트 싱크 맨 위로
they're real close to each other so oh
그들은 그렇게 서로 진짜 가까이있어 오
yeah I'm probably going to need to
그래 아마에 필요 해요
remove the speed limiter on the fan I'm
팬 의 스피드 리미터 를 제거합니다.
probably good oh yeah you find the fan
아마 아 좋아 팬을 찾는다.
is coming on because mine of course I
물론 내 것이기 때문에 계속되고있다.
switched to a cess DS so the fan just
DS 로 전환 하여 팬이되었습니다.
never even fires up but I did find it
결코 발사 할 수는 없지만 나는 그것을 발견했다.
was running quite a bit warmer when it
조금 더 따뜻해 졌어요.
had the spinning hard drives in it
그 안에 회전하는 하드 드라이브 가 있었다.
yeah okay surgery so I'm doing little
네, 괜찮아요. 그래서 조금 하고 있어요.
bits at a time yeah and how you've been
한 번에 조금씩 , 어떻게 지내 셨는지
doing it it's been good real real good I
그 일을하면 좋은 진짜 진짜 좋은 I이었다
just got to get a good hose I don't have
방금 가지고 있지 않은 좋은 호스 를 사야 해.
to wear the dog collar anymore oh yeah
더 이상 개 목걸이 를 착용 오 예
but I do have to keep my motion limited
그러나 나는 내 동작을 제한해야한다.
and I'm not supposed to he said he would
그리고 나는 그가 말하기로 되어 있지 않다.
have made me keep the collar on if I was
내가 있었다면 칼라 를 계속 붙이게 했다.
a tennis coach so oh yeah no back and
테니스 코치 그래서 오, 그래 다시는 아니야.
forth
앞으로
no no nodding no shaking my head yeah
아니 내 머리를 흔들어 끄덕 끄덕 없음
just take it easy take it easy
간단하게 받아들이 기 쉬워요.
yeah binge watch lots of category-five
네 binge 카테고리 5 많이 챙겨라.
been doing that that's for sure
그 일 을 확실히 해왔다.
your fans your favorite fans you must
팬은 좋아하는 팬을 수행해야합니다
our biggest fans on YouTube biggest fans
YouTube 가장 큰 팬의 가장 큰 팬
on YouTube you begin the kick out of
YouTube 에서 킥을 시작합니다.
that one I love it
한 것을 나는 그것을 사랑 해요
so good there's somebody that's gonna
잘 될 누군가가있어.
reply or yeah yeah I was I was tempted I
답장 또는 예 예 유혹을 받았다.
was curious whether we should tag the
우리가 태그를 달아야하는지 궁금했다.
people that were featuring I wasn't sure
내가 특징으로 했던 사람들 은 잘 모름
if you know I wasn't sure what the
당신이 알고있는 경우에 나는 무엇을 확신하지 못했습니다
reaction would be because it is very
반응 은 매우
very tongue-in-cheek where am I making
나는 혀를 아주 좋아한다.
fun of but at the same time we're
우리의 재미 는 있지만 동시에 우리는
turning it into a tutorial so that you
그래서 튜토리얼로 돌려 당신
can see yeah you know what the Odroid is
Odroid가 무엇인지 알 수 있습니다.
actually a little bit smaller than the
실제로는 조금 작은
Raspberry Pi taking the creative spin on
크리 에이 티브 스핀을 복용 라스베리 파이
that but so I'm glad that the response
하지만 그 대답 은 기쁘다.
has been good I think that you could
좋았어. 네가 할 수 있다고 생각해.
probably say the same and we weren't
아마 같은 말을 하고 우리는 그렇지 않았다.
really sure no no we weren't sure but it
정말로 우리가 확신하지는 못했지만
has been going amazing well I love it
훌륭하게 잘되어 가고 있습니다.
and I'm really hoping that the people we
그리고 나는 우리가 사람들이
actually do mention that they that they
실제로 그들은 그들이
eventually catch themselves like I feel
결국 내가 느끼는 것처럼 스스로 잡는다.
like right now some of them are just
같은 지금 그들 중 일부는 단지입니다
drawn to that one particular episode but
그 하나의 특정 에피소드로 그려 지지만
as they watch I feel like they'll
그들이 보는 것처럼 나는 그들이 느끼는 것처럼 느껴진다.
finally start seeing you know I've been
마침내 내가 너를 알기 시작했다.
in college well did the good thing is is
대학에서 좋은 점은 무엇입니까?
they're commenting on the on the
그들은 에 대한 의견 을 달고 있습니다.
technology piece you see that it's that
기술 조각 당신 은 그것을 볼 수 있습니다.
seven minute video on putting the case
사건 퍼팅에 관한 7 분 비디오
together which you don't do anything
함께 하지 마라.
you're standing off to the side they
너는 그들 편에 서있다.
need to watch the entire episode the
전체 에피소드 를 볼 필요가있다 .
whole hour
1 시간 내내
to see how you get the next you get the
어떻게하면 다음에 얻을 수 있는지 알아 보려면
next 20 to 30 minutes to do I know I'm
다음 20 ~ 30 분은 내가 난 알고하기
very lucky and you know what well well
매우 운이 좋았고, 당신은 잘 잘 압니다.
most of the tech stuff is going on a lot
대부분의 기술이 계속 진행되고 있습니다.
of times I'm in the chat room you know
당신이 아는 대화방 에있는 시간들
back and forth with the viewers then so
앞뒤로 시청자와 다음 그래서
I get a lot of interaction right on the
나는 마우스 오른쪽 상호 작용을 많이받을
spot which is fun yeah yeah we've we've
재미 자리 그래 우리는 우리가했습니다했습니다
chatted a couple of times yeah well do
몇 번 채팅 잘 했어.
you have any like you know this is an
너는 네가 알듯이 너는 이것이
opportunity for you as you're
니가 할 수있는 기회
interacting with us to ask any questions
질문을하기 위해 우리와 상호 작용 한다.
or any questions that have arisen as
또는 다음과 같이 제기 된 질문
you've been watching the show about the
당신은에 대한 쇼를 지켜 봤는데
technology or anything like that I know
기술 또는 내가 아는 모든 것
the only questions I had were about the
내가 가진 유일한 질문은
nems
nems
which unfortunately okay I think what
불행하게도 괜찮 생각하는 것
I'm what I'm gonna do is I'm just gonna
내가 할 일은 내가 할거야.
sign off now just because I know we're
이제 우리가 알기 때문에 그냥 사인해라.
coming into the tricky part and instead
까다로운 부분 으로 들어가서 대신
of just wondering whether or not I'm
단지 난 여부 궁금
actually live I'm gonna go now such a
실제로 살다. 나는 지금 이렇게 갈거야 .
great time we have to do this far more
우리가 할 일이 훨씬 더 많아
frequently absolutely all right all
자주 절대적으로 모든 권리
right
권리
Happy New Year and thanks for thanks for
새해 행복과 감사에 대한 감사
joining us from the road that's really
정말로 우리를 도로에서 탈락시키는
cool guys so what are you showing us
시원한 친구들 그래서 우리에게 보여주고있는 게 뭐야 ?
here Dave this looks like a pie cluster
여기 Dave 는 파이 클러스터처럼 보입니다.
of some sort that's Mike that's my pie
일종의 마이크가 내 파이 야.
cluster very nice eight Raspberry Pi 3
클러스터 아주 좋은 8 라즈베리 파이 3
sitting on top of a managed switch yeah
관리되는 스위치 예 위에 앉아
where I run I was testing out some
나는 어디에서 테스트를하고 있었는가?
parallel processing programs just
병렬 처리 프로그램 단지
playing around
놀고있다
yeah hey that's fun that's fun what are
그래 야 그 어떤 재미 재미
you using the cluster is
클러스터가 사용
what did I end up with hey hi
나는 안녕 안녕으로 끝났어.
for MPI for it's something oh yeah I
그것을 위한 MPI를위한 무언가 오, 그래요.
can't remember now
지금 기억할 수 없다.
okay I remember now that's something
좋아, 이제 그게 뭔가 기억 난다.
that that's something that I haven't
그건 내가하지 못했던 것이다.
tried yet is clustering my pies and part
시도는 아직 내 파이를 클러스터링 및 부분
of that is because jumping straight to a
그건 바로 점프하기 때문이다의
node Odroid you know there's so much
노드 Odroid 당신은 너무 많이 알고
more power in there so right so it
거기에 더 많은 권력이 있으니
almost seems like it's a fun project but
거의 재미있는 프로젝트처럼 보이지만
maybe not necessary at this point but
이 시점 에서 필요하지 않을 수도 있지만
yeah there were some questions when I
그래 몇 가지 질문이 있었다 때
mentioned in the chat room there were
대화방에서 언급이 있었다
some questions why would you do that and
왜 그런 질문을할까요?
I was like because I can because I've
내가 할 수 있기 때문에 나는 같았다.
got a dozen pies and I want to put them
12 개의 파이가 있고 나는 그들을 넣고 싶다.
up together make them into one super pie
함께 하나의 슈퍼 파이로 만들어라.
that's it I got eight down here I got
그게 내가 여기에 8 개 있어.
three upstairs I got a couple of pie
3 층 위층 에 파이 2 개가있어.
zeros just sitting around I did give a
그냥 주위에 앉아 0 제
bunch of them away you know my daughter
그들 무리가 내 딸 을 알지.
in college she's had friends that were
대학 에는 친구가 있었어.
mentioning it and I said here just I'm
그것을 언급 하고 나는 여기서 말했다.
giving him know what how much do you
너에게 얼마나 많은 돈이 있는지 알게 해줘.
want for my said I don't want anything
내 말은 하고 싶다. 나는 아무것도 원하지 않는다.
formed is the one proviso is is when
형성된 단 하나의 단서는
you're done with him you hand them off
당신은 당신이 그들을 손으로 그와 함께 완료
to somebody else yeah that's cool
누군가 다른 사람에게 그것은 멋지다.
that was the idea of the Raspberry Pi to
그것은 라스베리 파이 의 아이디어 였습니다 .
get you know get kids involved with
애들과 관련되게해라.
coding for next to nothing you know it's
당신이 아는 것 외에 옆에있는 것을위한 코딩
that's it's the whole point and and I
그게 요점과 난의의
think that was what God everybody wound
그것이 모두가 상처 입은 하나님 이라고 생각 합니다.
up when you called the Odroid the PI
당신이 Odroid를 PI 라고 불렀을 때
killer because there is so much so many
킬러 너무 많은 있기 때문에
people behind the Raspberry Pi it's it's
라스베리 파이 뒤에 있는 사람들
yes ridiculous it's ridiculous what do
네 말도 그것은 무슨 말도 안돼
you think Oh bill I mean between you and
당신은 내가 당신과 사이에 의미 오 법안을 생각
me not not like anyone else is ever
나는 다른 누구도 싫어하지 않는다.
going to see this but between you and me
당신과 나 사이하지만이 볼 것
it's done very well for us I know right
내가 잘 알고 우리를 위해 아주 잘 끝났다
like people don't realize as they
사람들은 깨닫지 못합니다.
comment and they you know condemn me for
댓글을 달았 습니다.
calling it a Raspberry Pi killer that
그게 라스베리 파이 살인자라고
we've had half a million views on that
우리는 그것에 대해 50 만 회의 견해를 가졌습니다.
video well I had part about it is it's
비디오 잘 나는 그것이 그것에 관해 일부 다 가지고 있었다
there they are in short supply the Oh
거기에 그들은 공급 부족 에 오
droids because they're on backorder
그들이 백 오더에 있기 때문에 드로이드
again are they now okay yeah yeah they
다시 그들은 지금 괜찮아요 그래, 그래
went currently on
현재에 갔다.
again if you go to Amazon if you use
당신이 아마존에 간다면 다시
your link it says currently on a bet
현재 귀하의 링크 가 내기에 표시되어 있습니다.
well they come from South Korea they're
그들은 한국에서 온 것입니다.
making them in badges right you can
배지에서 바로 만들 수 있습니다.
order them directly from hard colonel i
단단한 대령 으로부터 직접 주문해라.
think that's probably the best way to do
그게 아마도 최선의 방법이라고 생각해.
it but of course doing it that way they
그것은 물론 그렇게하는 것입니다.
don't have a partner program or anything
파트너 프로그램이나 다른 것을 가지고 있지 않다 .
like that for us so there's no kickback
우리에게 그런 식으로 그래서 리베이트가 없습니다
but at the same time you know we'll work
그러나 동시에 우리는 우리가 일할 것을 알고 있습니다.
on expanding you you know like it's
네가 좋아하는대로 확장 하는 걸 좋아해.
really tough for us to give links to
우리가 링크를 제공하기에 정말 힘든
products because they're all always
항상 제품이기 때문에 제품을
changing right so I set up the shop
내가 상점을 세우기 위해 권리를 바꾼다.
category 5 TV is an effort to give you
카테고리 5 TV 는 당신에게주는 노력입니다.
more options when you click on products
제품을 클릭 할 때 더 많은 옵션 제공
but it's hard to maintain it's hard to
하지만 유지하기가 어렵습니다.
keep up with you know we've mentioned a
당신은 우리가 언급 한 알과 유지
thousand products in the past year and
지난 해 제품 수천 개
then you know half of the links stopped
그러면 링크의 절반이 멈춘 것을 알 수 있습니다.
working it's pretty tough yeah yeah well
일하는 것은 꽤 힘들 네요.
but even on hard colonel if you go to
하드 대령 도 당신이 간다면
the site you scroll down to the xu4
사이트 에서 xu4로 스크롤 합니다.
it'll say ships in 21 days so they're
21 일 안에 배를 말하면서
even really you don't even have them you
심지어 정말로 너는 너를 가질 필요 조차 없어.
know Wow yeah actually sure yeah I was
알고 그래 실제로 있는지 그래 와우이었다
just curious about how he got into
그가 어떻게 들어 왔는지 궁금하다.
building all of these computer techie
이 컴퓨터 기술을 모두 구축 하십시오.
type things like what was your lead like
당신의 리드와 같은 것을 입력하십시오.
lead into it I have always been into
그것으로 인도한다 나는 항상
electronics I when I went to high school
전자 제품 내가 고등학교에 다닐 때
and went to a specialized High School in
에있는 전문 고등학교에 갔다 .
Brooklyn New York and and I took the
브루클린 뉴욕과 내가 데려
electrical course which was a basic
기본 전기 코스
intro into electronics then I went to an
전자 제품에 대한 소개는 다음 나는 갔다
electronics college and I started
전자 공학 대학과 나는 시작했다.
working at Xerox back in 83 and I just
83 년 Xerox에서 일하고 있습니다.
it just kept growing and growing and
그것은 계속 성장하고 성장했습니다.
growing and then we got into the
성장하고 나서 우리는
computers and stuff and now I am a
컴퓨터와 물건 과 지금 나는
system analyst at Xerox so but and it's
제록스에서 시스템 분석가 때문에 그러나 그것은이다
not the analyst type job that most
가장 애널리스트 유형의 직업이 아닙니다.
people think it's I help with the
사람들은 내가 도움이된다고 생각합니다.
presale and the implementation and post
presale 및 구현 및 게시
sale problem resolution of Xerox
제록스의 판매 문제 해결
equipment so we put them in site in
장비 그래서 우리는 그들을 사이트 에 넣어
customer sites connect them up to their
고객 사이트로 연결할 자신의
networks connect up third-party
네트워크가 제 3자를 연결합니다.
solutions for scanning printing
스캐닝 인쇄용 솔루션
copying is just we don't call them
복사는 우리가 그들을 호출 하지 않습니다.
copiers anymore that's there's so few
의 더 이상 복사기 그래서 몇 가지있다
copies made nowadays it's all on the
요즘 복사 된 것이 전부입니다.
scanning so I need to keep abreast of
스캐닝 때문에 나는 계속 지켜봐야한다.
everything so I know I have to know
그래서 나는 내가 알아야 할 모든 것을 알고있다.
Windows Mac Linux UNIX because some of
윈도우 맥 리눅스 유닉스의 일부 때문에
our some of our solutions are based on
우리의 우리의 솔루션의 일부에 기반으로
UNIX
유닉스
now that Solaris is gone son has dropped
이제 솔라리스가 사라졌습니다.
Solaris I think we're gonna start moving
솔라리스 이동을 시작한다고 생각합니다.
over to Windows but I still need to know
Windows로 넘어가지만 여전히 알아야 할
all the stuff so anything I can learn
내가 배울 수있는 모든 것들
just keeps me ahead of the curve yeah my
그냥 커브보다 앞서 나를 유지합니다.
job wow that's really me because I think
내가 생각하기 때문에 작업은 와우 그건 정말 나야
there is that connection I met a guy who
그 연결이 있습니다. 나는 사람을 만났습니다.
was I had like started tinkering with
내가 땜질을하기 시작 했어.
computers when he was a kid now he the
그가 어렸을 때의 컴퓨터
field of IT and it's just it's just
IT 분야이며 단지
something that there's like this
이게 뭐니?
connection from when you're young right
어렸을 때부터의 연결
start with something about a party come
파티에 대해 뭔가를 가지고 시작하자.
back together and then you understand
다시 함께하고 너는 이해한다.
something fundamental about something
무언가에 근본적인 무언가
and then it kind of builds upon there
다음은 가지가 기반으로 구축
and feel so exactly yeah I was I was
그리고 그렇게 정확하게 느낀다 나는 내가 존재했다.
always a tinkerer when I was a kid used
나는 아이가 사용되었다 항상 땜장이
to drive my parents crazy because they'd
그들이 부모님을 미치게 만들었 기 때문에
come home and see something and pieces
집에 돌아와 무언가를 보아라.
on the dining room table
식당 테이블에
oh that was me bill yeah but I always
오, 그건 내가 빌 법안 이었지만 항상 그래.
got back together what did you do to the
함께 돌아 왔어요.
VCR place all the tapes everything's
VCR 장소 모든 테이프 모두의
backwards
뒤로
oh boy I was tearing things apart what a
오, 소년 나는 무엇 을 찢어 버리고 있었다 .
world though now when you've got things
세상은 이제 당신이 물건을 얻었을 때
like raspberry PI's and OH droids and
나무 딸기 파이와 오하이오 처럼
everything Allison
모든 것 앨리슨
like it's so far changed from when we
지금까지 우리가 변화 했을 때와
were kids like my son who's 10 years old
10 살짜리 아들 처럼
we just got him the old-style
우리는 방금 그에게 구식을 얻었다.
electronic science kit you know the one
전자 과학 키트 당신이 하나를 알고
with the little Springs and you run the
작은 스프링과 당신은
cables I know right so this is a
케이블이 옳다 는 것을 압니다 .
throwback for me but it's also an
나를 위해 후퇴하지만 그것은 또한
opportunity for me to instill in my son
나에게 기회를 내 아들에 주입하는
some of the knowledge that I wish that I
내가 소원이 지식의 일부
had when I was a kid right growing up
나는 어렸을 때 자랐다.
and now I'm just now starting to
이제 지금 막 시작했습니다.
understand things like capacitors and
커패시터 및
relays and all this kind of stuff so for
릴레이를위한 그래서 물건의 모든 종류의
him to have that knowledge at 10 years
그 10 년의 지식을 가지고
old and into his later teen years then I
늙었 고 10 대 후반으로
think that's a good opportunity for him
그게 좋은 기회 라고 생각해.
to
에
be ready for being a builder and a maker
빌더와 메이커 인을위한 준비
because these guys
왜냐하면이 사람들
classic but they're great for teaching
고전 하지만 그들은 가르치는 데 아주 좋습니다.
the basics of you know how conductors
당신의 기본은 도체가 어떻게
work and how how you can create circuits
회로와 회로를 만드는 방법
and things like that but these days I
그런 것들을 좋아 하지만 요즘 나는
think I find that kids are taught in
나는 아이들이
school and we're starting to see this
학교와 우리는 이것을보기 시작 하고있다.
migration over to you know they're doing
그들이 너를 하고 있음 을 너에게 알게된다.
hands-on stuff but for so many years
손재주하지만 수년 동안
it's been learning the software learning
그것은 소프트웨어 학습을 배우고 있습니다.
how to use Microsoft Excel but not
Microsoft Excel에서하지만를 사용하는 방법
understanding well how do you work it if
당신이 그것을 어떻게 작동하는지 잘 이해 한다면
the icon is gone right exactly how does
아이콘 은 정확히 어떻게 사라 졌는가?
the computer itself work so yeah my only
컴퓨터 자체가 너무 좋아 내에서만 작동
exposure to circuits and that kind of
회로에 대한 노출과 그런 종류의
thing was in a physics class in high
물리학 수업 이 최고 였어.
school and we were given I don't blame
학교와 우리는 내가 비난하지 않는다 주어졌다
the teacher for this is a great teacher
이 선생님 은 위대한 선생님입니다.
but we were given a sheet and we had to
그러나 우리는 시트 를 받았고 우리는
like figure out how all the circuits
모든 회로를 이해하는 것처럼
were going to work and it took literally
일하게 될 것이고 그것은 문자 그대로 받아 들여 졌다.
like five hours for everyone and it was
모두를 위한 5 시간 같이
hard work and it was but it was not fun
열심히 하고 그것은 재미 있지만 아니었다.
having some hands on would have been a
되었습니다에 대한 몇 가지 손을 것 인
lot more interesting and having that
훨씬 더 흥미롭고
reward for having it work you know when
언제 일하는 것에 대한 보상 은 언제 알 수 있습니까?
it did work would've been amazing yeah
그것은 일 했을까?
I'm hoping that's what we're gonna see
그게 우리가 보게 될걸 기대 하고 있어.
with my son with this kit is that
이 키트 내 아들이다와
there's a there's a payoff yeah you know
네가 알고 있는 보수가 있다.
you're you're manufacturing a metal
너는 금속 을 만들고있어.
detector or whatever else yeah yeah you
감지기 또는 다른 무엇이든지 예.
know another thing to do Robbie I don't
로비 할 또 다른 일을 알아. 나는하지 않는다.
know if you thought of this oh he's
당신이 생각하는 경우 오 그가 알고
playing with his computer take away his
그의 컴퓨터로 놀아 라.
mouse and soon okay you you need to
마우스와 곧 괜찮아 당신을 수행해야
learn keyboard shortcuts interesting
재미있는 키보드 단축키 배우기
yeah yes there's a billion keyboard
예 , 10 억 개의 키보드가 있습니다.
shortcuts in in every operating system
모든 운영 체제의 바로 가기
and people forget that and it's like
사람들 은 그것을 잊어 버렸 습니다.
they get so reliant on the mouse it's
그들은 마우스에 너무 의존한다.
like take it away that's a great fight
그것을 빼앗아 가면 위대한 싸움 이야 .
built on my Christmas list this year and
나의 크리스마스 목록에 올해에 내장
I'm just gonna reach over because I've
내가 끝났어.
got it here I brought it with me to the
여기 있어요. 저와 함께 가져 왔습니다.
studio because it's gonna operate the
스튜디오가 작동 하기 때문에
teleprompter but this is one of the
프롬하지만이 중 하나입니다
things that my wife got me and it's a
내 아내가 얻은 것들 과
Bluetooth keyboard but I specifically
블루투스 키보드하지만 구체적으로
said I don't want a touchpad right for
나는를위한 터치 패드의 권리를하지 않을 것을
that very reason I do not like using a
나는를 사용하여 좋아하지 않는 바로 그 이유
mouse when I'm setting up systems and
마우스를 사용 하여 시스템을 설정할 때
you know I'm in the terminal and that's
당신은 내가 터미널에있어 알고 그건
that's a really cool point yeah
그건 정말 멋진 포인트 예요.
I should get a new Bluetooth keyboard
나는 새로운 블루투스 키보드를 얻어야 한다.
because I don't use the touchpad it has
내가 터치 패드를 사용하지 않기 때문에이있다
it but I don't like using it and my palm
그러나 나는 그것과 나의 손바닥을 사용하는 것을 좋아하지 않는다.
ends up hitting it oh yeah I really like
이 오 그래 내가 정말 좋아 타격 끝
this little hey I just learned less as a
이 작은 이봐 난 그냥 덜 배웠다
party at my place that New Year's party
내 파티에서 파티 그 새해 파티
and you were just talking about keyboard
너는 방금 키보드에 대해서 말하고 있었다.
shortcuts and the literary press shift
단축키와 문학 보도진 이동
apparently seven times I can hold it
분명히 일곱 번 내가 그것을 붙들 수있다.
down too long it locks a keyboard into
너무 오랫동안 키보드 를 잠급니다.
symbols loud mm-hmm okay I did not I
기호를 큰 소리로 mm-흠 좋아 나는하지 않았다
have never in my like 20 years of using
20 년 동안 같이 사용 하지 못했습니다.
computers ever like come upon this ever
컴퓨터는 이제까지 이것 같이 온다 좋아한다
press the shift key for too long I've
Shift 키를 너무 길게 누르면됩니다.
just never done that I guess I've never
한 번도 한 번도 해본 적이 없어.
held it for longer than you know 10
당신이 알고있는 것보다 오랫동안 그것을 가지고 있었다. 10
seconds or number of times by accident
실수로 초 또는 횟수
so a lot of people nuts is when your
그래서 사람들 너트 많은 경우 당신의
keyboard automatically this happens in
키보드가 자동으로
Windows automatically switches languages
Windows가 자동으로 언어를 전환 함
I get phone calls from people to say I'm
나는 사람들로부터 전화 를 받으면서 내가
trying to put in my password and this
내 비밀 번호를 넣어 려고
putting in all these crazy characters
이 모든 미치광이 캐릭터 퍼팅
and I'm like have you typed any words
나는 네가 어떤 단어라도 타이핑 한 것과 같아.
like resume lately switch their keyboard
최근 이력서처럼 키보드를 바꾼다.
to French mode and now everything's in
프랑스어 모드로 전환했습니다.
the wrong place and you were trying to
틀린 장소와 당신 이하려고 노력하고 있었던
get the the pipe yes on the Raspberry Pi
라스베리 파이 에 파이프를 가져와.
yeah I think that we're doing like a
그래 나는 우리가 같은 일을하고 있다고 생각
retro pie setup or maybe Plex
레트로 파이 설정 또는 아마도 Plex
yeah yeah it's it's because the pie
예, 맞아요 파이 때문 이예요.
comes down to faulted to Great Britain
영국에 착오를 일으킨다.
mm-hmm yeah and they they've got all
mm-hmm 그래, 그들은 모두 가지고있어.
those special characters on the top row
맨 위에 있는 특수 문자
are all different I'll tell you what
모두 다르다. 나는 너에게 무엇을 말할 것이다.
Bill it was pretty quick that all of our
빌. 우리 모두가
biggest fans on YouTube let me know
YouTube의 가장 열렬한 팬이 저에게 알려줍니다.
about that that's what we're finding so
즉, 우리가 찾고있는 무엇 그것에 대해
we keep a smile on our faces and
우리는 우리의 얼굴에 미소를 유지하고
approach it with a bit of
약간의 방법으로 접근
tongue-in-cheek
혀를 넣다
that's it well I'm looking forward to
그게 다야. 나는 기대 하고있다.
everything that's gonna happen in 2018
거 2018에 일어날 모든
lots of stuff happening hey like we've
우리가 한 것처럼 많은 일들이 일어나고있어.
got the four
네 개 있어.
okay camera run I'm on a 4k tonight
괜찮아 카메라가 달리다 오늘 밤에 4k에있어.
today right here this is just the
오늘 여기가 바로 여기에 있습니다 .
Panasonic but it actually has the I can
파나소닉하지만 실제로 할 수있다.
talk about it now because she's gone
그녀가 떠나서 지금 그것에 대해 이야기하십시오.
it's got the teleprompter it's got the
그것이 텔레 프롬프터를 가지고 있습니다.
teleprompter on it and I tried it for
그것에 teleprompter와 나는 그것을 위해 시험해 보았다.
the first time the other day and it I
다른 날과 내가 처음 으로
have a new respect for for Sasha it's
사샤 에게 새로운 존경심 을 가져라.
tough to run a teleprompter and read it
텔레 프롬프터를 실행 하고 읽는 것이 어렵다.
from the screen but it's kind of cool
화면에서하지만 멋진 일종의
when you showed it to me that's why I
네가 그걸 나에게 보여 줬을 때 그게 내가 왜
made the comment because I know it's my
내가 내 이름인지 알기 때문에 의견을 냈다.
eyesight I would never be able to do
시력 나는 결코 할 수 없을 것이다.
that no yeah are you able to do that and
그럴 수 없다는 것과
I see she wears glasses too yeah good
나는 그녀가 좋은 그래 너무 안경을 착용 참조
for her so it's out its out of the box
그녀 를 위해 상자에서 나온 것입니다.
but that's what we have on the camera
하지만 그게 우리 카메라에있는거야.
now yeah nice so but then I've got this
지금은 그래 좋은 그렇게하지만 내가있어이
camera here this is the the HM 170 which
여기 카메라는 HM 170입니다.
is slowly growing but the lens ring
천천히 성장하지만 렌즈 링
adapter didn't fit so I had to order a
어댑터는 너무 맞지 않았던 나는 주문했다
like just an eight dollar lens adapter
8 달러짜리 렌즈 어댑터 처럼
to extend it out a little bit so that
그래서 조금 그것을 밖으로 연장
the the teleprompter will fit on this
이 텔레 프롬프터는 이것에 적합합니다.
one because this one we're reviewing in
하나 는 우리가 검토 중이기 때문 입니다.
two weeks so that's kind of quite mm-hmm
2 주 정도면 꽤 긴장 되네요.
so lots lots you know the show should
많이 많이 그래서 당신은 쇼를해야 알
look a lot better in the next couple of
다음 커플 에서 더 좋아 보인다.
weeks and I'm starting to move around
주와 나는 움직이기 시작하고있다.
the set because we've lost the
세트는 우리가 잃어 버렸기 때문에
green-screen here people complain when
여기 녹색 화면은 사람들이 불평 할 때
we're standing up that the you know the
우리는 당신이 알고있는 것을 위로 하고 있습니다.
logo is down there right not realizing
로고가 아래로 권리 실현되지 않습니다
that this is actually meant to be a sit
이것이 실제로 앉아있을 운명 이라고
down set with interview seats and stuff
아래 인터뷰 좌석과 물건 설정
like that we've used it a few times but
우리는 그것을 몇 번 사용했습니다 것을 좋아하지만,
then when we got this desk I had to move
우리가이 책상을 가져 왔을 때 나는 움직여야했다.
everything here but then I never kind of
여기있는 모든 것, 그렇다면 결코
finalized it so it was always kind of a
그것의 종류가 항상 친절했기 때문에 그것을 마무리했다 .
temporary solution but ended up being a
임시 방편이 아니라를 었죠
little more permanent than I am then I
더 영구적 인 작은 내가 그때 나보다
didn't intended so but the the
그런 의도 는 아니 었지만
green-screen doesn't work on the 4k
녹색 화면 이 4k에서 작동하지 않습니다.
because our server the computer that I
우리 서버는 내가
use for Wirecast is too slow for that
Wirecast를 열고 대한 사용은 너무 느리다
because it's you know that's a lot of
이 때문에 당신은이를 많이 알고
stuff to do live chroma key with a 4k
4k로 라이브 크로마 키를 할 물건
camera but it worked fine on the 1080p
카메라 가 1080p 에서 정상적으로 작동했습니다.
so what I'm thinking about doing is
그래서 내가이 일에 대해 생각하고
putting the green screen back to where
녹색 화면을 어디로 되돌려 놓을까요?
it used to be on the other side of the
그것의 다른쪽에 예전
room so that we've got a nice green
우리가 좋은 녹색을 가지고 있도록 방
screen news room like we used to have
우리가 가지고 있었던 것처럼 스크린 뉴스 룸
and then switching everything back to
모든 것을 다시
the brick set
벽돌 세트
and then rebuilding this into an
이것을 다시
interview set so so we should have a
인터뷰가 설정되어 있으므로
pretty nice setup within the next
다음에서 꽤 좋은 설정
handful of weeks anyway so I'll be a lot
어쨌든 일주일에 한 번 내가 많이있을거야.
of work you really if you really want to
당신이 정말로 원한다면 정말로 일하는 것의
wind up your your your biggest fans
가장 열렬한 팬들을 감동 시키십시오.
bring them back to episode one yeah with
그들 과 에피소드 1로 다시 데려 와라.
the webcam it was 140 P now with 4k
웹캠 그것은 지금 4k와 140 P했다
we're like which 4k camera do we like
우리는 4k 카메라가 우리가 좋아하는 것과 같습니다.
durable cam that was classic we have a
우리가 가지고있는 고전적인 내구성있는 캠
webcam on a gerbil cage I like that
gerbil cage의 웹캠
going for a 4k run has a double meaning
4k 달리기 는 두 가지 의미가 있습니다.
there we're doing a 4k run this
우리는 4k를 실행 하고 있습니다.
afternoon right so you're also going for
오후에 너도 같이 가겠다 .
a you're going for a run this afternoon
오늘 오후에 너 뛰고 있어.
no no I just saying when you said that
아냐, 네가 그렇게 말했을 때 말했어.
you're doing a 4k run I was like I was
네가 4k 달리기를하고 있어.
like no I'm not doing anything in the
아니, 아니 .
snow it's like you travel even just
눈 은 마치 당신이 여행하는 것과 같습니다.
walking for the vehicle yeah great
예를 들면 위대한 자동차를 위해 걷기
message no Robbie does not do 4k runs in
Robbie가하지 않는 메시지는 4k에서 실행됩니다.
the snow bill doesn't do 4k runs in the
눈금은 4k를 뛰지 않는다.
summer well she's ooh Jeff well Jeff is
여름 잘 그녀는 우입니다. 제프 잘 제프입니다.
sorta here I think he's watching but
여기는 그가보고있는 것 같아.
unable to actually communicate back with
실제로와 다시 통신 할 수 없습니다
us I see he posted a couple things in
우리는 그가 몇 가지를 게시 한 것을 본다.
the chat there said he's here says he
거기있는 채팅이 그가 여기에 있다고 말했어.
can see in here bill and said hi to
여기 빌에서 볼 수 있고 안녕하세요.
Sasha Jeff was in are you guys watching
사샤 제프가 너들보고 있니?
the chat says he was in New York in
그 채팅은 그가 뉴욕 에 있었다고 말한다 .
November he bypassed all the toll
11 월 그는 모든 통행료 를 우회 했다.
stations his car is very fast yes Sasha
그의 차는 매우 빠르다 예 사샤
was asking about tolls down in New York
뉴욕에서 통행료를 묻고 있었어.
and they were just brutal yeah I think
그리고 그들은 단지 잔인한 예라고 생각합니다.
they take our money any way they can
그들은 우리가 할 수있는대로 돈을 가져 간다.
no I got you so he was he was listening
아니, 내가 듣고 있었을 정도로 너를 잡았어.
in a nice cute yep yeah he's there he's
좋은 귀여운 예, 예, 그는 거기에 있어요.
there yes I don't see and this is my
거기에 네, 보지 못해요 그리고 이것은 내 것입니다.
first time ever using
이제까지 사용하여 처음으로
google hangouts so if I start clicking I
Google 수다방을 클릭하면
might lose you so I'll take your word
너를 잃을 지 모르니 너의 말을 들어 줄게.
that he's in the chat area this is cool
그가 채팅 영역에 있다는 것은 멋지다.
and we're gonna do this my plan as you
우리는 너처럼 나 한테이 계획을 할거야.
know is to do the this monthly so
이걸 매월 이렇게 하는 것이 좋습니다.
hopefully we'll have a good turnout you
잘하면 우리는 좋은 투표율을 가질 거야.
know moving forward of course bill
코스 계산서 앞으로 나아가는 걸 압니다.
you're our only patron that is here
너는 여기있는 유일한 후원자 야.
that's exclusively a patron but you know
그건 독점적으로 후원자 지만 너는 알고있다.
we'll probably see this grow as more
우리는 아마도 이것이 더 많은 것으로 자라는 것을 볼 것입니다.
people catch on and our patreon page has
사람들이 캐치하고 우리의 애송 페이지에는
been growing over the past little while
과거에 조금씩 자랐다.
I hope that you've liked the changes
나는 당신이 변화를 좋아했기를 바란다.
that I've made there it's been a lot of
내가 거기에서 만들었던 것은 그것이 많이 있었다.
us yeah so trying to try to make it more
우리는 그래 그래서 더 만들려고 노력
interactive more exciting things like
대화 형 흥미 진진한 것들
the Google Plus the Google hangout that
구글 플러스 구글 행 아웃이
kind of stuff mm-hmm
종류의 물건 mm-hmm
so hopefully we'll see you grow yeah I'm
잘하면 우리는 네가 성장할 것을 볼 거야.
reading Jeff says my camera on my
독서 제프는 내 카메라가 내
monitor is no longer functioning and I
모니터 가 더 이상 작동하지 않고
don't have a mic hooked up to the
마이크를 집어 넣지 마라 .
monitor there you go so he's here he's
그가 거기에 있는지 모니터 해라. 그가 여기에있다.
here in spirit
여기 정신에
thanks for being here Jeff she's always
여기와 주셔서 고맙습니다 제프 는 항상
a pleasure to see you we could do this
우리 가이 일 을 할 수 있다는 것을 보게되어 기쁘다.
even as part of the show sometimes like
때로는 쇼의 일부로 좋아해요.
you know use this as an opportunity for
이걸 기회로 사용 하는 거 알아.
viewers to communicate with us and ask
시청자가 우리와 대화하고 질문하십시오.
questions or something like that that
질문이나 그런
might be fun yeah looks like it works
작동처럼 그래 재미있을 것이 보인다
pretty good bill thank you for being
꽤 좋은 계산서가 당신에게 감사드립니다.
here
이리
you broke the ice for our patrons on
너 우리 후원자들을 위해 얼음을 부러 뜨 렸어 .
Google Hangouts so thank you no problem
Google 행 아웃은 아무 문제가 없으므로 고맙습니다.
yeah we didn't have a great day happy
예, 우리는 행복한 하루를 보내지 않았습니다.
happy new year again and here's to a
새해 복 많이 받으세요 .
wonderful year for all of us with
우리 모두 를 위한 멋진 해
category-five and and personally as well
카테고리 -5 그리고 개인적으로
and all the best to to everyone yeah
모든 사람에게 최선 을 다합니다.
Happy New Year guys thank you for having
새해 복 많이 받으신 분들께 감사드립니다.
me
나를
see y'all take care
너 모두 잘 봐라.